(Penny:)Yeah, you've been
going out
(Sheldon:)for years.
You haven't even slept together.
(Sheldon:)That's right.
It's called foreplay.
(Sheldon:)And I could make the case
(Sheldon:)that you two aren't moving
forward in your relationship.
(scoffs)
Uh,
(Sheldon:)hello.
(Sheldon:)Hello.
(Penny:)No. Sheldon,
we're getting married.
(Sheldon:)But you've been engaged
for over a year now,
(Sheldon:)and you don't even have
a wedding date.
(Penny:)Well, we will. We're
just not in a rush.
(Penny:)Okay.
(Leonard:)We're gonna set a date.
(Sheldon:)Okay. If you say so.
(Penny:)Yeah, it's just, things
are good right now.
Really good.
(Penny:)I'm focusing on my job.
And we've been busy
with our paper.
(Penny:)So busy.
Yeah, we'll pick a date
when we pick a date.
(Penny:)Yeah.
(Penny:)Okay.
(Penny:)You know, I can see
why Amy's mad at you.
(Sheldon:)Yeah, shut up,
Sheldon!
(Bernadette:)Did you eat
all my yogurt?
(Howard:)You mean the one that
makes ladies do the thing